nwmls.com 2019-12-22

# Northwest MLS

#### Privacy Policy

### NWMLS Privacy Statement

##### Your privacy is our priority

NWMLS is committed to protecting its member's financial information. This Privacy Statement answers some questions about what personal information NWMLS collects, what they do with it, and how they protect it.

NWMLS collects personal contact information to include contact phone numbers, home address, email addresses and fax numbers.

During transfer of such information NWMLS uses several security devices and practices to include Firewalls, Secure Socket Layers (SSL) and Encryption. Security of member data is of the highest importance to NWMLS and is treated as such.

##### Common Questions:

 **Q.** Is my Financial Information shared with other companies?

 **A.** No. Financial information is not shared with any other company or member.

 **Q**. What types of personal information about me do you share?

 **A.** NWMLS may disclose personal information about you that we collect, primarily to make available to other members and subscribers. An example is that your contact information is distributed to other Broker Sites and also into the listing database. We do not disclose personal information about former members to anyone.

 **Q.** Does NWMLS sell our information to other companies?

 **A.** No it does not. NWMLS distributes contact information as per the NWMLS Broker Distribution. NWMLS Rules and Bylaws that apply to the Downloading Policy include Rule 27 and Rule 183.

 **Q.** What kind of security are you using to protect my Credit Card number?

 **A.** NWMLS uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal account information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. NWMLS treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

 **Q.** Can NWMLS change the privacy rules?

 **A.** Yes. NWMLS may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our site.

 **Q.** This is all confusing. Can I contact someone for help in understanding the privacy statement or answer my Specific questions?

 **A.** Yes. Contact NWMLS at 425-820-9200 or 800-541-0455 for any questions relating to security of the NWMLS site or privacy.

 **Q.** Can I help with the security?

 **A.** Yes. The best and easiest way for NWMLS members to keep the site secure is to protect your password by not sharing it with anyone. Use a separate password for NWMLS.com and IMS web sites. Change your password every few months to ensure security.
